Guide to the UE News Photograph Collection, 1933-1998 UE.14.1
ULS Archives & Special Collections
UE News Photograph Collection
1933-1998
ULS Archives & Special Collections
United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America
UE.14.1
46.25 Linear Feet (37 boxes)
This collection contains photographs dating from 1933 to 1998 which were primarily used by the United Electric, Radio, and Machine Workers of America's newspaper, the UE News. These photographs document UE conventions and local functions; plant openings; international labor tours; politicians and other union presidents; and general union members. Digital reproductions of selected images are available online.
History
In 1939, the UE News replaced the People's Press as the official newspaper of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America. The UE News is comprised of articles regarding the union, photographs of prominent UE officers and labor activities, and political cartoons. Today, the UE publishes this newspaper eight times a year.
Scope and Content Notes
This collection contains photographs dating from 1933 to 1998, the majority of which where taken between 1946 and 1989. These photographs depict many individuals who were UE members, politicians, or important to the union through there work with a company or labor relations. The majority of the photographs contained within the collection were taken in the United States of America and Canada. However, several other countries are represented, including but not limited to: Chile, El Salvador, the European Union, Guatemala, Haiti, Japan, Mexico, Nicaragua, Puerto Rico, and the Soviet Union. Such photographs involve international labor tours, conventions, plant openings, and international union establishment. Many of the photographs contain captions assigned by the newspaper editors. A selection of the images from this collection can be found online.
Arrangement
Photographs contained within the Convention series are arranged chronologically. District photographs are arranged numerically beginning with District 1 and ending with District 12. Districts contain locals situated by geographical areas. Locals are arranged first numerically followed by Farm Equipment and those which deviate from numerical order. Individual and Topic photographs are arranged alphabetically.
Missing Title
Series 14.1.1. National Convention, 1936-1995
Series 14.1.2. Districts and Locals, 1940-1998
Series 14.1.3. Founding Officers
Series 14.1.4. Individuals
Series 14.1.5. Oversize Photographs
Series 14.1.6. Chicago UE News Photographs
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America in in several accessions dating from 1975 to the present.
Previous Citation
UE News Photograph Collection, 1933-1998, UE.14.1, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Existence and Location of Copies
Digital reproductions of the collection are available electronically at http://historicpittsburgh.org/collection/united-electrical-radio-machine-workers-america-ue-records.
Related Material
UE News Records, 1936-1990, UE.12, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Photographs; Erie (Pa.); Philadelphia (Pa.); Pittsburgh (Pa.); Labor; Electric industry workers -- United States; Chicago (Ill.); Electric industry workers -- Labor unions -- United States; Labor unions -- United States – Congresses; Matles, James J.; Carey, James B.; Carter, Jimmy; Chavez, Cesar; Darin, Margaret; DuBois, W. E. B. (William Edward Burghardt); Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Dwight David); Emspak, Julius; Fitzmaurice, David; General Electric Company; Jandreau, Leonard; Kennedy, James; McCarthy, Joseph; Murray, Philip; Newell, Charles; Philadelphia Storage Battery Company; Quinn, Thomas J.; Radio Corporation of America; Scribner, David; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America. Convention; Westinghouse Electric Corporation; Wright, Fred
- National Conventions, 1936-1995; 14.1.1.
  Scope and Contents note
  This series spans from the founding Convention in 1936 thru the 60th Convention in 1995. Files are arranged chronologically and contain some photographic negatives. Material contained within the photographs focuses on leaders and delegates addressing the convention audience.
  - Founding Convention, Buffalo, March 1936 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1st Convention, Fort Wayne, Indiana, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 3rd Convention, St. Louis, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 5th Convention, Springfield, MA, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 6th Convention, Cleveland, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 7th Convention, Cleveland, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 8th Convention, New York City, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 9th Convention, New York City, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 10th Convention, Cleveland, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 11th Convention, Milwaukee, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 12th Convention, Boston, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 13th Convention, New York City, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 14th Convention, Cleveland, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 15th Convention, New York City, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 16th Convention, New York City, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 17th Convention, Cleveland, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 18th Convention, Chicago, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 19th Convention, New York City, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 20th Convention, Cleveland, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 21st Convention, New York City, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 22nd Convention, San Francisco, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 23rd Convention, New York City, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 24th Convention, Chicago, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 25th Convention, Atlantic City, NJ, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 26th Convention, New York City, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 27th Convention, Long Beach, CA, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 28th Convention, New York City, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 29th Convention, New York City, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 30th Convention, New York City, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 31st Convention, Pittsburgh, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 32nd Convention, San Francisco, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 33rd Convention, New York City, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 34th Convention, Philadelphia, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 35th Convention, Atlantic City, NJ, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 36th Convention, Los Angeles, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - 37th Convention, New York City, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - 38th Convention, Pittsburgh, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 39th Convention, New York City, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 40th Convention, San Francisco, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 41st Convention, Cleveland, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 04-05)
  - 42nd Convention, New York, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 06-07)
  - 43rd Convention, Minneapolis, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - 44th Convention, New York, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - 45th Convention, Los Angeles, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - 46th Convention, Pittsburgh, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - 47th Convention, New York, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - 48th Convention, Philadelphia, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - 49th Convention, New York, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - 50th Convention, Milwaukee, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - 51st Convention, New York, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - 52nd Convention, Boston, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - 53rd Convention, Pittsburgh, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - 54th Convention, Chicago, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - 55th Convention, Los Angeles, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 56th Convention, Pittsburgh, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 57th Convention, Baltimore, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 58th Convention, Cleveland, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 59th Convention, Pittsburgh, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 60th Convention, Burlington, VT, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Districts and Locals, 1940-1998; 14.1.2.
  This series contains photographs depicting individuals and events of specific union districts and locals.
  - Local 101: Philco, Philadelphia, 1942, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Local 102: Philco, Philadelphia (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Local 103: RCA, Camden, 1940s (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Local 108: Gould Battery and National Battery, Trenton and Philadelphia, 1942-1944, 1967, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Local 109: Bendix-Friez, Baltimore, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Local 111: New Jersey and Philadelphia, 1966-1968 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Local 112: Ingersoll-Rand, Phillipsburg, NJ (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Local 113: Exide Battery, Philadelphia, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Local 114: Bendix Corp, Philadelphia (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Local 115: General Electric, York, PA, 1949, 1955-1957 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Local 117: Babcock and Wilcox, Honesdale (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Local 118: Insulated Wire, Philadelphia, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Local 119: General Electric, Philadelphia, 1942, 1949-1950 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Local 120: Locke Insulator, Baltimore, 1952-1989 (Box 5, Folder 14-15)
  - Local 121: Clendenin Brothers, Baltimore, 1966-1989 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Local 122: Duralite, Baltimore (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Local 123: GE, Staunton, VA, 1956-1989 (Box 5, Folder 18-19)
  - Local 124: RCA, Lancaster, 1940-1950 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Local 124: GE, Waynesboro, VA, 1965-1979 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Local 124: GE, Waynesboro, VA, 1980s-1990s (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Local 125: GE, Scranton, 1940s-1970s (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Local 125: Stanley, Mastic, Cox Creek, 1980s-1990s (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Local 127: Staunton, VA, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Local 128: GE, Allentown, 1957-1985 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Local 130: Baltimore (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Local 131: Edison Spitdorf, Hellertown (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Local 132: Champion Blower, Lancaster (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Local 134: Ferracute Machine Co. and Holman, Bridgeton and Merchantville, NJ, 1949, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Local 136: Proctor Electric, Philadelphia, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Local 137: Westinghouse, Wilkes-Barre, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Local 139: Keystone Watch Case, Riverside, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Local 141: Penn Pump and Cooper Industries, Easton, 1942, 1985-1993 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Local 143: Allentown (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Local 144: National Vulcanized Fibre, Wilmington (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Local 145: Harowe Servo Controls (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Local 149: Western Electric, Allentown, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Local 155: Tool and Die and Willard Jacquard Knitting Machine Co., Philadelphia, 1945-1979 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Local 155: BVI and Stryher and Harowe Servo, 1980-1989 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Local 155: AMSCO, Hatboro, PA, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Local 156: Willard Jacquard Knitting Machine Co., 1957-1965 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Local 157: Automatic Timing Controls, Philadelphia, 1959-1979 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Local 158: Jerrold Electronics Inc., Philadelphia, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Local 159: Cuther Metal Products Co., Camden, 1965-1982 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Local 160: Chester Morton Electronics, Chester, PA, 1965-1970 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Local 162: Globe Rubber Co., Philadelphia, 1966-1970 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Local 162: RCA, Pulaski, VA, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Local 165: Chester, PA, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Local 166: Formiqli Co., Berlin, NJ (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Local 168: Penn Supply Co. and Rois Mfg., Philadelphia, 1968-1989 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Local 170: Foster Wheeler Plant, Mountaintop, PA, 1970-1982 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Local 171: Fagersta Steel Company, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Local 174: Cardo and SMS Automotive and Penn Brake, 1981-1991 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Local 175: Argo Co., Berwick, PA, 1981-1985 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Local 179: Penn Vent, Philadelphia, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Local 198, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - District 1: General (Box 6, Folder 01-03)
  - District 1: Contact Sheets, 1972-1989 (Box 6, Folder 04-07)
  - Local 201: GE, Lynn, MA (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Local 202: Archer Daniel Midland and Westinghouse, Hudson, NJ and Springfield (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Local 203: GE, Bridgeport (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Local 204: GE, Taunton, 1952-1972 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Local 204: Haskon Corporation, 1980-1989 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Local 205: GE, Ashland, MA, 1957-1977 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Local 205: Telechron, Ashland, MA (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Local 207: Landers, Frary, and Clark, New Britain (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Local 209: Westinghouse Bryant Electric HEMCO, Bridgeport, 1946-1975 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Local 209: Westinghouse Bryant Electric HEMCO, Bridgeport, 1975-1980 (Box 7, Folder 10-12)
  - Local 210: Manning, Maxwell and Moore, Bridgeport (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Local 210: Bridgeport Plating, Bridgeport, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Local 210: F.Dyne; Bridgeport Plating; Beacon, Bridgeport (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Local 212: E.D. Jones and Beloit, Pittsfield, MA (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Local 212: Beloit, Dalton, MA (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Local 213: Van Norman Tool, Springfield (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Local 214: Holtzer Cabot Electric Co., Roxbury (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Local 214: Prince (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Local 215: Lynn, MA (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Local 216: Lynn, MA (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Local 217: Elliott Addressing Co., Cambridge (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Local 218: Jones and Lamson; Whitelight Co.; Parks and Woolson; Vermont Foundaries Inc.; Bryant Chucking Grinder Co.; N. Walpole, NH; Springfield, VT, 1947-1989 (Box 7, Folder 24-28)
  - Local 219: Trimount Plastics Co.; Carol Cable; Columbia Electric, New Bedford, MA (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Local 221: Goldfeder Co., National Automatic Products, 1958-1960 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Local 222: Sylvania, Salem (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Local 223: Crown Wire Workers, Taunton, MA, 1980-1989 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Local 224: A.S. Campbell, GE, East Boston (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Local 225: Maguire Industries, Bridgeport (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Local 226: Bacon Felt Co., Taunton, MA, 1980-1989 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Local 227: Singer Sewing Machine, Bridgeport (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Local 228: Paragon Gear Co., Taunton, MA (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Local 230: Charles Parker Co., Meriden, CT (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Local 232: Fairbanks, Morse and Co., St. Johnsbury, VT, 1946-1978 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Local 233: Cooper Thermometer Bristol, CT (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Local 234: Fairbanks Morse and Co., St. Johnsbury, VT, 1980-1989 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Local 235: Union Mfg. Co., New Britain, CT (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Local 236: Standard Nut and Bolt Co., Pawtucket, RI (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Local 236: Standard Nut and Bolt Co., Pawtucket, RI (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Local 238: Murray Carver Inc. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Local 240: GE, Bridgeport (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Local 243: Sargent Co., CT, 1946-1989 (Box 8, Folder 10-11)
  - Local 244: Beacon (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Local 248: Modern Plastics, Taunton, MA (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Local 249: Hartford (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Local 251: Pratt and Whitney, Hartford, CT (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Local 252: Remington Arms, Bridgeport (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Local 253: Submarine Signal Co., Boston (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Local 254: GE, Pittsfield, MA (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Local 255: GE, Pittsfield, MA (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Local 257: Lynn (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Local 258: Pre 1960 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Local 258: Cone Automatic Machine, Windsor, VT, 1968-1978 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Local 258, 1980-1989 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Local 259: Worthington Pump Co.; TRW Wire, Holyoke, MA, 1944-1979 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Local 259, 1980-1989 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Local 260: Ingraham Co., Bristol, CT (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Local 262: H.K. Porter Co.; Manning, Maxwell and Moore Co.; Cole Hersee Co.; A.S. Campbell CO.; Keystone, Boston, 1949-1966 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Local 262: H.K. Porter Co.; Cole Hersee Co.; Cambion; WBCN, Boston, 1970-1979 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Local 262: H.K. Porter Co.; Cole Hersee Co.; WBCN, Boston, 1980-1989 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Local 263: Watham Watch, Lynn (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Local 264: Holyoke, MA (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Local 265: Royal Typewriter, Hartford, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Local 269: Smith and Wesson; Irving Paper, Springfield, MA, 1944-1989 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Local 270: Rhodes Manufacturing, Hartford CT (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Local 270: GE, Hartford, 1980-1989 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Local 271: GE, United Shoe Machinery Corporation, Beverly, MA, 1954-1989 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Local 272: Cole Hersee (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Local 273: Stanley Tool, Staftsbury, VT, 1980-1989 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Local 274: United Greenfield Co.; Greenfield Tap and Die, Greenfield, MA, 1942-1969 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Local 274: Miller Falls Tool Co.; WESCO; Greenfield Tap and Die, Greenfield, MA, 1957-1979 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Local 274: WESCO, Greenfield, MA, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Local 274: Miller Falls Tool Co.; WESCO; Greenfield Tap and Die, Greenfield, MA, 1980-1989 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Local 275: Turner Tanning; Viking Aluminum, Peabody, MA and New Britain, CT, 1980-1989 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Local 276: Union Twist Drill, Athol, MA (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Local 277: National Silver Co.; Morse Twist Drill, New Bedford, MA, 1955-1979 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Local 277: Morse Cutting Tool, New Bedford, MA, 1980-1989 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Local 279: Atwood and Morrill, Salem, MA, 1958-1979 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Local 282: Winchester Repeating Arms, New Haven, CT (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Local 284: Submarine Signal Co.; J.C. Rhodes; Fall River, New Bedford, MA (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Local 284 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Local 286: Fitchberg (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Local 290: New Process Twist Drill, Taunton, MA (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Local 291: Maxim Motors, 1971-1990 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Local 292: Reliable Steel Drum, Fairfield, CT (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Local 293: Essex Macallen, Newmarket, NH, 1972-1979 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Local 294: Sylvania, MA (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Local 295: Bijur Lubricating Co., Bennington, VT, 1958-1978 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Local 296, 1968-1987 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Local 297: GE, Lowell, MA, 1948-1988 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Local 298: A. Henkel Inc.; Whitney Brake, Keene, MA and New Haven, CT (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Local 299: HARCO; Whitney Brake, New Haven, CT, 1958-1979 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Local 299: Circuit Wise, HARCO, Branford, CT, 1980-1989 (Box 9, Folder 15-17)
  - District 2, 1942-1989 (Box 9, Folder 18-26)
  - District 2: General (Box 9, Folder 27-28)
  - Local 301: GE, Schenectady (Box 10, Folder 01-03)
  - Local 304: North Tonawanda (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Local 305: Blackstone, Jamestown, NY (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Local 306: Spaulding Fiber, Tonawanda (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Local 307: Dahlstrom, Jamestown, NY (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Local 308: Remington Rand, Tonawanda (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Local 310: GE, Elmira (Box 10, Folder 09-10)
  - Local 311: Star Expansion, Newburgh, NY (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Local 312: North Tonawanda (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Local 313: Syracuse (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Local 316: Schenectady Chemical, Schenectady (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Local 318: Remington Rand, Syracuse (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Local 319: Battenfeld Grease and Oil Co., North Tonawanda (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Local 320: Syracuse (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Local 321: Easy Washer, Syracuse (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Local 322: GE, Fort Edward, Hudson Falls (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Local 323: Globe Forge and Foundry, Syracuse (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Local 324: Fairbanks Value Co., Binghamton (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Local 325: Jamestown Metal Products, Jamestown, NY (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Local 326: Markel Electric Co., Buffalo, NY (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Local 327: Remington Rand, GE, Johnstown City, Westover (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Local 328: Technical Appliance Corp., Sherburne (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Local 329: Liberty Tool and Die, Rochester, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Local 329: Kennedy Value, Elmira, 1966-1990 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Local 331: General Cable Co., Rome, NY (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Local 332: GE, Hudson Falls, Fort Edward, 1952-1979 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Local 332, 1980-1989 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Local 333: Mica Insulator Co., Schenectady (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Local 334: GE, Rochester (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Local 335: Sylvania, GE, Jamestown and Buffalo (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Local 336: Ferranti Packard, Dunkirk, NY (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Local 370, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Local 180 UE FE: International Harvester, Auburn (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Local 1581 UE FE: Westinghouse, Buffalo and Cheektowaga (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Local 501: Buffalo (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Local 509: Rochester (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - District 3 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - District 3: Remington Rand (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Local 401: Singer Sewing Machine, Elizabeth, NJ (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Local 402: Thermatron, Long Island, NY (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Local 403: Hatfield Wire and Cable, Hakettstown (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Local 404: Anaconda Wire and Cable, Hastings (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Local 404: Tungsten Alloy (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Local 404: Median Corporation, NJ, 1980-1990 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Local 405 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Local 406: Universal Corrugated Box Machinery Corporation (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Local 407: Thomas A. Edison Industries, Orange, NJ (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Local 408: Star Electric Motors, Bloomfield, NJ (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Local 409: Kramer Trenton Refrigerator Co., Trenton (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Local 410: Westinghouse, Bloomfield, NJ (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Local 411: National Pneumatic, Rahway (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Local 412: Westinghouse Lamp Division, Bloomfield, NJ (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Local 414: Kroydon Golf Club Mfg. Co., Maplewood, NJ (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Local 414: SussmanCo., Perth Amboy, NJ (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Local 415: American Transformer Co., Newark (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Local 415: Lazzara Co. (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Local 416: Eastern Aircraft, Bloomfield, NJ (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Local 416: Mallory Randall Corp., Brooklyn (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Local 417: Bendix Corp., Red Bank, NJ (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Local 417: Bijur and Groov pin, Ridgefield, NJ and Rochelle Park, NJ (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Local 417: Groov pin, 1980-1990 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Local 418: Becton Dickenson, East Rutherford (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Local 419: General Electric, Mt. Vernon, NY (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Local 422: General Electric, Bloomfield, NJ (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Local 425: Ford Instruments, NYC (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Local 426: Westinghouse, Newark (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Local 427: Keuffel and Esser Co., Hoboken, NJ (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Local 428: Sonotone, White Plains, NJ (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Local 429: General Electric, Newark (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Local 430 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Local 431: Calculating Co., Orange, NJ (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Local 433: Tung-sol, Bloomfield, NJ (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Local 434: P.R. Mallory Co., Tarrytown, NJ (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Local 435: Walker Turner, Plainfield, NJ (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Local 436: General Instrument Corp., Newark (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Local 437: Coxhead, Newark (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Local 440: Foster Wheeler, Carteret (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Local 441: Phelps Dodge, Elizabeth, NJ (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Local 443: Westinghouse, Trenton (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Local 444: Pyrene Mfg., Newark (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Local 445: National Union Radio, Newark (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Local 446 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Local 447: International Telephone and Radio (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Local 448: Groov pin, Callite Tungsten, Union City, NJ (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Local 448: A. Johnson Machine Co., Paterson, NJ (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Local 450: Sperry, Brooklyn (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Local 451: Ingersoll Rand, Phillipsburg, NJ (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Local 452: Liquidometer, Sunnyside, NJ (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Local 453: Otis Elevator, Yonkers (Box 11, Folder 51)